<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KenyaGuide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView text</string>
    <string name="textview1">TextView1 text</string>
    <string name="Masai">most known in eastAfrica</string>
    <string name="ethnicGroups">EthnicGroups</string>

    <string name="karibukenya">Karibu Kenia Mombasa</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaDescription">Safari-Experience in connection with a relaxin Holiday at the Kenyan coast.</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaDescription1">14 Days, inc. FlyingTicket</string>
    <string name="KaribuKenyaDescription2">From € 2799 p.P.</string>
    <string name="KaribuKenyaZanzibar">Karibu Kenya and Sansibar</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaZanzibardDes">Combine your Kenya Safari with a relaxing Holiday  at the exotisch Island of Zanzibar.</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaZanzibarDes2">14 Days, einschl. Flugreisen</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaZanzibarDes3">from € 2959 p.P.</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaDubai">Karibu Kenya and Dubai</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaDubai1">Safari in Kenya in connection with Luxuryholiday in dubai.</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaDubaiDes2">13 Tage, einschl. FlyingTicket</string>
    <string name="karibuKenyaDubaiDes3">from € 2909 p.P.</string>
    <string name="wildMombasa">Mombasa and the wild Kenya</string>
    <string name="wildMombasaDes">Experience unbelieveble Animals in 3 Nationalparks, followed by relaxing swimming Holida in Mombasa.</string>
    <string name="wildMombasaDes2">14 Days, inc. FlyingTicket</string>
    <string name="wildMombasaDes3">from € 2349 p.P.</string>
    <string name="masaiMaraDescription">Maasai Mara (Masai Mara) is situated in south-west Kenya and is one of Africa’s Greatest Wildlife Reserves. Together with the Serengeti National Park in Tanzania it forms Africa’s most diverse, incredible and most spectacular eco-systems and possibly the world’s top safari big game viewing eco-system.</string>
    <string name="masaiMaraGamePark">MasaiMaraGameParks</string>
    <string name="abedareDescription">The fertile slopes of the central Highlands were recognised by European settlers as being great farming country for tea, coffee, wheat and flowers. Many came and took the land with the colonial government\'s blessing. There was little regard for tribal land or local customs and this created great resentment, which erupted into the bloody Mau Mau Rebellion of the 1950\'s.</string>
    <string name="abedareGameReserve">AbedareGameReserve</string>
    <string name="nairobiNationalParkDescription">A short drive out of Nairobi’s central business district is the Nairobi National Park. Wide open grass plains and backdrop of the city scrapers, scattered acacia bush play host to a wide variety of wildlife including the endangered black rhino, lions, leopards, cheetahs, hyenas, buffaloes, giraffes and diverse birdlife with over 400 species recorded. Visitors can enjoy the park’s picnic sites, three campsites and the walking trails for hikers.</string>
    <string name="nairobiNationalPark">NairobiGamepark</string>
    <string name="meruNationalParkDes">Meru National Park is noted for its fauna and natural beauty. It has many swamps and rivers lined with palms, as well as mountains and woodlands, and it is the setting for Joy Adamson\'s book \"Born Free\", which was later made into a successful film. The park is home to a large pride of lions, herds of buffalo, and hippos and crocodiles that live in the rivers.</string>
    <string name="meruNationalParkDes2">At Meru, you will find excellent views of snow-capped Mount Kenya and the park\'s beautiful landscape is a camper\'s paradise. The roads are suitable for vehicles and there are many rocky outcrops that provide great lookout points for the abundant Kenyan animals.</string>
    <string name="meruNationalParkDes3">Meru National Park facts</string>
    <string name="meruNationalParkDes4">Overview and summary of Meru National Park</string>
    <string name="MeruNationalParkDes5">Climate and weather in Meru National Park</string>
    <string name="meruNationalParkDes6">How to get to Meru National Park</string>
    <string name="meruNatuionalParkDes6">What to see and what to do at Meru National Park</string>
    <string name="meruNationalGamePark">MeruGamePark</string>
    <string name="KikuyuDescription">he Kikuyu (also Akikûyu) are the largest ethnic group in Kenya. They speak the Bantu Kikuyu language. At a population of 6.6 million as of 2009, they account for close to 17% of the total population of Kenya.</string>
    <string name="kikuyuTribe">kikuyu Tribe</string>
    <string name="masaiTribe">Masai Tribe</string>
    <string name="kambaTribeDescription">The Kamba or Wakamba people are a Bantu ethnic group-or tribe-who live in the semi-arid formerly Eastern Province of Kenya stretching east from Nairobi to Tsavo and north up to Embu, Kenya.</string>
    <string name="kambaTribe">Kamba Tribe</string>
    <string name="meruTribeDescription">Meru people. The Meru, Amîîrú, \"Ameru\" or Ngaa people are a Bantu ethnic group that inhabit the Meru region of Kenya on the fertile lands of north and eastern slopes of Mount Kenya, in the former Eastern Province of Kenya.</string>
    <string name="meruTribe">Meru Tribe</string>
    <string name="turkanaDescription">Turkana people. The Turkana are a Nilotic people native to the Turkana District in northwest Kenya, a semi-arid climate region bordering Lake Turkana in the east, Pokot, Rendille and Samburu people to the south, Uganda to the west, and South Sudan and Ethiopia to the north.</string>
    <string name="turkanaTribe">Turkana Tribe</string>
    <string name="masaiTribeDescription">Maasai people. The Maasai (Kenyan English: [maˈsaːɪ]) are a Nilotic ethnic group inhabiting southern Kenya and northern Tanzania. They are among the best known local populations due to their residence near the many game parks of the African Great Lakes, and their distinctive customs and dress.</string>
    <string name="sarovaStanleyWebsite"> About us->http://sarovastanley.com-nairobi.com/</string>
    <string name="sarovaSternleyHotel">Sarova Stanley</string>
    <string name="hiltonHotelDescription"><![CDATA[About us->http://www3.hilton.com/en/hotel-locations/ke/index.html]]></string>
    <string name="hiltonHotel">Hilton Hotel</string>
    <string name="emeraldHotel">Emerald Hotel</string>
    <string name="emeraldDescription"><![CDATA[About us->http://thehotelemerald.com/]]></string>
    <string name="salamaHotel">Salama Hotel</string>
    <string name="salamaHotelDescription"><![CDATA[About us->https://www.salama-beach-resort.com/]]></string>
    <string name="turkanaHotels">Turkana Hotels</string>
    <string name="turkanaHotelDescription"><![CDATA[About us->https://www.tripadvisor.de/Hotels-g480201-Turkana_District_Rift_Valley_Province-Hotels.html]]></string>
    <string name="EthnicGroups">EthnicGroup</string>
    <string name="gameParks">GameParks</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="safari">Safari</string>
</resources>
